黑 鏡
僅供學習 禁止用于任何商業盈利行為
最新最快海外影視字幕下載
原創翻譯  雙語字幕
翻譯：根總迷弟 沫沫 鹽湖涼開水 癢癢
校對：草草
時間軸：林卡
后期：吉吉  總監：草草
黑函之舞
肯尼  四號桌弄撒了很多食物  不好意思
Kenny? Big spillage on table four. Sorry.
好了  走吧
Okay. All right.
稍等
Excuse me.
有人忘了這個哦
Someone forgot this.
謝謝
Oh, thank you!
-你該說什么  -謝謝
- What do you say? - Thank you.
-不客氣  -她總是丟三落四的
- It's all right. - She forgets everything.
再次感謝
Thanks again.
她是個瑜伽老師  身體韌性超好
She was some yoga teacher, proper bendy.
你看  快看
Look. Look.
天啊  我操  那是她發給你的嗎
Jesus! Fuck! What, she sent that to you, did she?
調皮又淫蕩
Double naughty.
滾開
Jog on.
琳子
Linds!
琳子  我的筆記本電腦呢
Linds, where's my laptop?
-別這么混蛋  -用你自己的去
- Don't be a bell end! - Use your own.
-我的壞了  你的也凍住了  -你干了什么
- Mine's bust. Yours has gone all frozen. - What did you do?
我只是想安裝個看電影的軟件
I was trying to put on this film thing.
什么看電影的軟件
What film thing?
我也不知道  就是讓你能免費看電影的程序
Don't know. Some programme lets you watch free films.
我在安裝的時候  電腦就被鎖住了
While I was trying to put it on, then it locked up.
聽著  這不是我的錯
Look, it's not my fault.
別再拿我的電腦了  又不是你的
Don't take it again. It's not yours.
等你修好你的  把我的也修一下吧
Oh, fix mine when you've done that.
"等你修好你的  把我的也修一下吧"
"Fix mine when you've done that."
重啟
贏智能手機
清除惡意軟件
利用懺悔神器清除惡意軟件
清除您電腦上的惡意軟件
恢復機密  找回信心
免費下載
正在下載  懺悔神器  惡意軟件清除者
正在進行診斷
清除惡意軟件
-別再偷喝我的可樂了  -隨便吧
- Stop nicking my Cokes! - Whatever.
那是你自己畫的嗎  肯尼
Did you draw that yourself, Kenny?
謝謝  肯尼  明天見
Thanks, Kenny. See you tomorrow.
再見
Bye.
-再見  肯尼  -再見  肯尼  明天見喲
- Bye, Kenny. - Bye, Kenny, I'll see you tomorrow.
你簡直瘋了
You're mental.
-你是個瘋子  -你是個賊
- You're mental. - You're a thief.
親愛的  肯尼  你覺得怎么樣
Love? Kenny? What do you think?
-我還是不習慣這個發色  -很漂亮
- I'm still not used to the colour. - It's nice.
是嗎
Yeah?
幫個忙  把你妹妹看住  行嗎
Do me a favour and prison-guard your sister, will you?
我不會玩到很晚的  應該不會
I won't be late. Probably.
天啊  他就在外面  冰箱里有千層面
Oh, my God! He's outside. There's a lasagna thing in the freezer.
我愛你
I love you.
發件人  ???  主題  你好
我們看到你干什么了
將你的手機號碼回復過來
否則我們就將本段視頻發送給你的全部聯系人
...將本段視頻發送給...
發送
您的消息已經發出
一條新信息  來自未知號碼
打開手機定位服務
保持一直開機  電量充滿
等時間到了  你就會被激活
你是誰
你是想要錢嗎
不準告訴任何人
我們在監視
你看到我的鑰匙了嗎
Have you seen my keys?
你沒事吧  肯
You okay, Ken?
親愛的
Love?
嗯  沒事
Yeah, fine.
早啊  肯尼
Morning, Kenny.
一條新消息  來自未知號碼
你被激活了
服從  否則我們泄露視頻
去這個位置  今天中午12點
定位  黑石路  工業區
我在工作
45分鐘內趕到  否則我們泄露視頻
15英里  騎行需57分鐘
-肯尼  -我很不舒服
- Kenny? - Feeling really sick.
-你才剛到呢  -我知道
- You've only just got here. - I know but
我覺得我可能會吐出來
think I might throw up.
好吧  但是下一次你能不能...
Okay, just next time can you- - ?
淡定  白癡
Easy, knobber.
6英里  18分鐘后到達
別遲到  你還有90秒
我到了
等著
拿著
Come on.
-是易壞品  -是什么東西
- It's fragile. - What is it?
是他們叫我交貨拍照的
They told me to do that.
這就完了嗎  我現在要怎么做
Is that it? What do I do now?
我也幫不上你
I can't really help you.
我要做些什么
What do I have to do?
照他們說的做  等你做完了  就可以退出了
Just whatever they say and once you've done that, you're out.
他們就會放過你
They let you off.
確認收貨
輸入盒子上的號碼進行驗證
把包裹送到該位置  121號房
我愛你
維海文賓館  房價最低60英鎊起
誰啊
Hello?
送快遞的
Del- - Delivery.
找錯房間了
Wrong room.
他們說是121號房
They said 121.
不  我沒有快遞
No, there's no delivery here.
-但他們說...  -我什么都沒訂購
- But they said- - - I haven't ordered anything.
是個蛋糕
It's a cake.
-什么蛋糕  -我不知道
- What cake? - I don't know.
好像是海綿蛋糕
I think it's a sponge.
我沒訂蛋糕  所以你送回蛋糕房去吧
I didn't order a cake so just take it back to the bakery
-就說他們搞錯了  -聽著  如果我...
- and tell them they got it wrong. - Look, if I- -
我不要那蛋糕  請你走開
I don't want the cake. So go away
否則我叫前臺了
or I call the front desk.
他不肯開門
就說是明迪叫你來的
我會把蛋糕塞進你的屁股里
I will kick that cake up your fucking arse.
是明迪叫我來的
M- Mindy sent me.
這是怎么回事  明迪在哪
What is this? Where's Mindy?
他們叫我把這個給你
I was just told to give this to you.
-明迪叫的嗎  -不是
- Mindy told you? - No.
你剛說了"明迪"
You said "Mindy."
是他們叫我這么說的
That's what they told me to say.
滾進去
Get inside.
你什么意思  你是說蛋糕是明迪訂的嗎
So what are you saying? Are you saying Mindy ordered the cake?
不  我也不知道  是他們
No, uh, I don't know. It- - they- - it was them.
他們  什么他們  你他媽在說什么
Them? They? Who the fuck are you on about?
-那些人  -哪些人啊
- The people. - What fucking people?
就是手機上的那些人  用手機聯系我的人
The phone people. The people on the phone.
他們叫我把蛋糕送過來
They told me to bring the cake,
他們不斷往我的手機上發信息
and they're leaving texts on my phone,
我就按照他們的指示去做
and then I do what they say.
慢點
Slow down.
用鼻子呼吸
Just breathe through your nose.
用鼻子呼吸  明白嗎
Through your nose. Okay?
很好  現在讓我看看他們說了什么
Good. Now, just show me what they said.
把手機拿出來
On your phone.
-讓我看看短信  -好吧  這個
- Show me the text. - Okay, well, um... This.
-我該...  -閉嘴  讓我自己看
- I should- - - Shut up. Just let me.
這他媽是什么玩意
What the fuck is this?
-這是些什么人  -我不知道
- Who are these people? - I don't know.
-你又是誰  -我跟他們不是一伙的
- Who are you? - I'm not them.
他們給我發信息  我就照他們說的做
They send me messages, and I do what they say.
為什么  你為什么要那么做
Why? Why would you do that?
是他們發來的嗎
Is it them?
我能走了嗎
不能
拍他
-他們說我必須這么做  -天啊
- They said I had to do that. - Jesus Christ!
好吧  好吧
Okay, okay.
他們要我們按照他們的指示去做
They're saying they just need us to follow their instructions,
一切都不會有問題的  好嗎
and everything will be okay. Okay?
該死
Shit!
他們說  我們必須一起完成
They're saying we have to do it together.
-我們要做什么  -把蛋糕送去某個地方
- What do we have to do? - Just take the cake somewhere.
他們把地址發我了  一個地圖坐標什么的
They sent me an address. A map coordinate thing.
-我們得去開一輛車  -車  什么車
- And there's a car we need to get. - A car? What sort of car?
我也不知道是什么車
I don't know what sort of car.
他們說就停在外面的停車場里
They said it's in the car park outside.
他們把車牌號發給我了  我就知道這些
They sent me a licence plate. That's all I know.
為什么要我們一起
Why both of us?
我不知道
I don't know!
你他媽先讓我把鞋穿好
Just let me deal with my fucking shoe, please.
他們說了什么
What have they said?
他們說 "跟他一起去  帶上貨物"
They say, "Go with him. Take the package."
好吧
Okay.
V760DHM
"V760 DHM."
車牌是V760DHM
V760 dhm.
我都要患上數盲癥了
I'm getting fucking number blindness here.
在那里
That's it.
好吧  他們說鑰匙放在后車輪上
All right. They said the keys are on the back.
找到
Okay.
聽著  或許該由你來開  你會開車嗎
Look, maybe you better drive. Do you drive?
我剛剛喝過酒
I mean, I had a drink back there.
我不能  我是會開車的
I can't. I can- - I can drive.
但我還在學駕駛
I'm still learning.
-還沒通過駕考  -好吧
- Haven't passed my test yet. - All right.
你來導航
You're navigating.
好吧  你手機上有衛星導航功能嗎
Okay, you've got a sat nav on your phone?
有的
Yep.
就這里  輸進去
Here it is. Punch that in.
在城外的某條路上  靠近高威科姆鎮
It's a street somewhere out of town. Sort of High Wycombe-ish.
他們讓我們在兩點前趕到  時間很緊
They said we got to be there by two. It's gonna be tight.
他們一定掌握了你的什么把柄吧
So I'm guessing they got some shit on you
威脅要公布出去吧
that they're threatening to put out?
至于我  是...
With me, it's...
你也看到那個房間了  有蕾絲內褲
You saw the room, fucking lacy knickers.
我其實在等一個妓女
I was waiting for a prostitute.
應召女  雞  現在有各種叫法
Escort, hooker, whatever they call them now.
我有家庭  那很好
I got a family, which is great.
人有時會無聊
You get bored.
我年輕的時候  喜歡...
I mean, when I was young, I used to like...
我沒辦法為自己找個正當理由
I can't fucking justify it.
我就是想操個20多歲的年輕姑娘
I just wanted to fuck a 20-something.
為了紀念過去吧  我也說不清
For old times' sake, I don't know.
我登陸了一個網站  我很好奇
I joined this website. I was curious.
就是想看看上面有什么
Just wanted to see what was on there.
我跟明迪聊上了  至少我以為她叫明迪
I got talking to Mindy, who I thought was Mindy.
她給我發了些照片  我也回復了一些
I mean, she sent me pictures. I sent some back.
手機自拍照  握住我自己的雞巴
Phone photos. Grabbing my cock.
你能想到的都有  他們全掌握了
You name it. They got the whole fucking thing.
不僅是照片  聊天記錄
But not just pictures, chat messages.
包括所有的安排  時間地點等
All the arrangements, where and when.
我在那兒討價還價  他們說他們全都掌握了
Me haggling over the price and they say they got it all.
像審計員一樣  把硬盤的信息全抽干了
Sucked up the whole hard drive like an audit.
該死的混蛋  我真是個大白癡
Fucking twat. What a fucking idiot!
如果那些信息泄露出去  我妻子就會離我而去
If that shit gets out, that's my wife out the door.
她還會把孩子們也都帶走
Then there's the kids, she'll take them.
我毫不懷疑  她會帶走他們
Oh, no, not a doubt in my mind she'd take them
而且她會打贏官司
and she'd win.
她會獲得監護權
Custody, she'd win.
我跟你說  我絕不能失去我的孩子們
And I'm not losing my kids. I tell you that right now.
不行  絕對不行
No way! Absolutely fucking no!
他們拍下了我
They filmed me.
-拍下了你...  -通過我的電腦攝像頭
- Filmed you... - Through my computer camera.
-拍下了你什么  -是的  就是
- What, like, filmed you? - Yeah, like,
干那事
you know, doing it.
-做愛嗎  -不是  就是...
- Like sex? - No. Like, you...
你懂的
you know.
打飛機
Jerking off.
看黃片打飛機嗎
Jerking off to porn or something?
大家都這么干
Well, everyone does that.
該死的教皇大概也這么干
The fucking pope probably does that.
他們要把它到處發
They're gonna put it everywhere.
要發給所有人
Like they're gonna send it to everyone.
-該死  真見鬼  -怎么了  怎么了
- Oh, shit the fuck! - What? What?
-指示燈亮了多久了  -什么燈
- How long's that light been on? - What light?
這車的主人  一點油沒剩
Whoever's car this is, they left it fucking empty.
一會兒就好
I won't be a minute.
無鉛汽油  無鉛汽油
Unleaded. Unleaded.
該死
Oh, bugger!
聽著  你去付錢  好嗎  這樣快一些
Listen, you pay, yeah? It'll save time.
你有錢嗎
Have you got any money?
好  維薩卡  密碼3109  重復一遍
Okay, Visa card PIN number 3109. Say that back to me.
-維薩卡  -說密碼
- Visa card-- - Just the number!
-3109  -好  快去
- 3109. - Okay, go!
4號泵
Pump four!
-幾號泵  -4號
- What's your pump number? - Four.
-來點巧克力嗎  -不了
- You want some chocolate? - No.
-買一贈一  -不用了
- It's two for one this week. - I'm okay.
31.89英鎊
31.89.
輸入密碼
Pop your PIN in.
輸入密碼  按"確認"鍵
密碼錯誤  重新輸入
處理中  請稍候
交易成功  請取出卡
-你確定沒問題嗎  -對  當然沒問題
- If you're sure you don't mind? - No, no, of course not.
我去辦  打幾個電話就好
I'll get on to that. Make some calls.
太好了  是在下周三
Brilliant! It's next Wednesday.
-好  -保險起見  不要含乳制品
- Okay. - Keep it non-dairy just to be safe.
好的
Okay.
這是...
This is, uh...
我侄子
my nephew.
很高興見到你
Nice to meet you.
-肯尼  -肯尼  我是凱倫
- Kenny. - Kenny. I'm Karen.
我們都是K打頭的
We're both Ks.
我是希奧和凱西學校的家庭教師協會會長
I'm head of the PTA at Theo and Cassie's school,
真是自作自受
for my sins.
我剛剛纏著霍克特
Just roped poor Hector into
為今晚的小測試之夜解決餐飲問題
sorting out the catering for the quiz night.
又要手忙腳亂了
Been the usual balls up.
那個  我得送這家伙去火車站了
Listen, we better get this guy to the station.
他的火車要...
His train's...
我們得趕緊了
So we better go.
-坎斯路火車站嗎  -對
- Cansroad Station? - Yeah.
能麻煩你送我到我家街道的盡頭嗎
Oh, couldn't drop me at the end of my road, could you?
和你們同路  梅耶街
It's on the way. Mayer Street?
不然我只能乘公交車了
It's the bus otherwise
公交路線太繞了
and that goes all the way around the common.
我們時間比較緊
We're in a bit of a rush, actually.
不用繞道  和你們同路
Well, it's no detour. It's en route.
到了我就跳下車  都不用減速  好嗎
I'll hop out. Hardly need to slow down. Yeah?
-好  行  走吧  -太好了  多謝
- Yep. Sure. Let's go. - Brilliant. Thanks!
我坐后面吧
I'll just get in the back.
把你的盒子壓到可不好
Oh, don't want to squash your box.
-那是什么  禮物嗎  -蛋糕
- What's that? Present? - It's a cake.
-就是...給佩妮的蛋糕  -她真幸福
- It's just a-- it's a cake for Penny. - Oh, lucky her.
佩妮怎么樣
So how is Penny?
上次見她還是在...好像是運動會那天
Haven't seen her since... must have been sports day.
她挺好
She's good.
-她還是想回去工作吧  -是啊
- She still planning to get back to work? - Yeah. Yep.
一條新信息  來自未知號碼
我們看見你們的定位了
兩條新信息  來自未知號碼
你們的方向不對
-希奧現在幾歲了  -七歲
- I mean, how old's Theo now? - Uh... He's seven.
我們看見你們的定位了
他演話劇時真有趣  戴著那頂大禮帽
He was so funny in the play. That big top hat on.
是啊  他演得很開心
Yeah, he had a good time.
你們的方向不對
安娜要開個通宵派對
Anna's having a sleepover.
凱西大概已經告訴你了
Cassie's probably already told you about it.
六個九歲大的孩子湊一起  我真是瘋了
Six nine-year-olds in the house. I must be mad!
三條新信息  來自未知號碼
掉頭
肯尼  你是要回哪里去
So, Kenny, where you heading back to?
-抱歉  什么  -你是要回家嗎
- Sorry. What? - Are you going home or...?
趕火車  去伯明翰
Train. Birmingham.
對
Yeah.
對  我家在伯明翰
Yeah, I-I live in Birmingham.
我丈夫就是那里的
My husband's from Birmingham.
-你在伯明翰的哪里  -南部
- What part are you? - South.
南部
South.
-算是吧  -這樣
- Mainly. - Right.
掉頭
你一直都住那里嗎  你聽起來不像...
Have you always lived there? 'Cos you don't sound--
我沒有那里的口音  是對  大家都說
I don't have the accent, no. Everyone says that-- that...
我的口音聽起來不像
I don't have the accent.
20分鐘內到位
我不在那里長大  我在別處長大
Didn't grow up there though. I grew up somewhere else.
倫敦  我在倫敦長大
Like London. I grew up in London.
否則我們就公開一切
這樣
Okay.
你爸爸媽媽是霍克特還是佩妮的親戚
And is your mum and dad on Hector's side or Penny's?
有人過街  過街
Someone crossing! Crossing!
抱歉  他要趕不上火車了
Sorry about that! Can't miss his train.
我到了
This is me.
見到你真好  肯尼
Great to meet you, Kenny.
代我向佩妮問好  好嗎
Give my best to Penny, won't you?
-當然  -那再見了
- Yes, of course. - Bye, then.
-再見  凱倫  -再見
- Bye, Karen. - Bye.
第一時間下載無刪減美劇  必須登錄字幕組網站
6英里  5分鐘后到達
我們會趕上的  好嗎
We're gonna make it, okay?
這個叉口就是了
It's this junction.
更好更快的原創翻譯 雙語字幕
-什么  這個嗎  -沒錯  沒錯
- What? This one? - Yeah, yeah, yeah.
你確定是這里嗎
You sure this is it?
"看蛋糕里面"
"Look in the cake."
我們看看蛋糕里面吧
Let's look in the cake.
我愛你
看蛋糕里面
Look in the cake.
應該是在蛋糕里面吧
In the cake, I suppose.
摸到了
I got something.
什么東西
What the fuck?
老天啊
Oh, my God.
"5分鐘決定"
"Five minutes to decide."
決定什么
Decide what?
-"誰開車"  -"誰搶劫"
- "Who is driver?" - "Who is robber?"
國家聯合銀行
不  不行
Oh, no. No.
-我們不能  我們...  -我開車
- W-w-we can't. We... - I'm driver.
你說你不能開車  那就我開
You said you can't drive. I'm driver.
我就在這里等  不熄火
I'll be right here with the engine running.
我們不能  我們...
We-- We can't. We--
那我們要怎么辦  肯尼
Then how else are we gonna deal with this, Kenny?
-我不會...  -聽我說
- I'm not-- - Listen to me.
-我不會...  -閉嘴  聽好了
- I'm not-- - Shut up and listen!
有帽子和墨鏡  沒人能認出你
Hat and sunglasses. No one's going to ID you.
你可能是任何人  這是第一點
You could be Kevin fucking Bacon. That's point one.
閉嘴
Shut up!
第二點  發生搶劫時  銀行人員經過訓練
Point two, in a robbery, staff are trained.
我不會...
I am not--
他們經過訓練  要交出現金
They are trained to hand over the cash.
不抵抗  我在紀錄片里看過
No argument. I saw it in a documentary.
不會有反抗  看起來很簡單
No resistance. It looked easy.
這不簡單
It's not easy.
我知道這不簡單
I know it isn't easy,
可我們還能做什么呢
but what the fuck else are we gonna do?
如果這個泄露出去  我會失去我的孩子
This gets out, I will lose my kids.
我對上帝發誓  如果那真的發生了
And I swear to God, I will stand in the kitchen
我會在廚房里找把切面包的刀刺穿我的喉嚨
and put a fucking bread knife through my throat if that happens.
我只是看了寫照片...
I only looked at pictures and--
然后在鏡頭下打了個飛機
And beat one off on camera?
他們都拍下了  對嗎
That's what they got, yeah?
你熱撲撲的小臉  模糊的拳頭
Your hot little face, blurred fist,
射得到處都是
dick burping fucking spunk everywhere?
你媽媽會很高興這些出現在臉書
Your mum's gonna love that on Facebook,
推特  還有什么他媽的圖片分享上
Twitter, Insta-fucking-whatever.
還有她的朋友  大家都會看到你做那個
And her friends. All eyes on you, giving it that.
再加上單位的死八婆  叫你"噴射小王子"
Toss in the cunts at work, calling you Spurty McGoo.
嘲笑你高潮的表情  把它設成電腦桌面
Laughing at your come face, making it their desktop wallpaper.
這不是幾個星期的事  好幾年都不會有人忘記
It's not just weeks. We're talking years here.
照片一谷歌就能搜到  就像吉普賽人的詛咒
Pictures hang about on Google like a gypsy fucking curse.
互聯網上的東西無可救藥  永遠不會消失
There's no cure for the Internet. It would never go away.
它會跟你的名字粘在一起  成為永遠的污點
It'd be glued to your name, a fucking stain on you.
如果那種事發生在我身上  我會自殺的
I'd hang myself if that was me.
一有機會就弄斷我的脖子
Crack my fucking neck at the first opportunity.
他們只是想要錢  那就進去把事做了
They just want the money, so go in there and do it.
-你會開車走人的  -我不會那樣做
- You'll drive away. - I am not gonna drive away.
我會坐在這里  車子不熄火
I'm gonna be sat here with the engine running.
我做不到  做不到
I can't. I can't.
-你可以的  你能做到  -我不行  真不行
- You can. You can. - I can't. I can't. I can't. I can't.
-你可以的  -我不行
- You can. - I can't.
我們沒時間了  肯尼
We don't have much time, Kenny.
這不是真的  這不是真的
It's not real. This is not real.
你能做到的
You can do this.
撐住  挺住
Keep it together. Please hold it together.
閉嘴  閉嘴  閉嘴  閉嘴
Shut up, shut up, shut up! Shut up!
好吧
Okay.
你有包嗎
Have you got a bag?
眼鏡  用鼻子呼吸
Glasses. Breathe through your nose.
給我錢
Give me money.
快給我錢
Just give me money!
-行  好吧  -我要很多錢  很多錢
- Yes. Okay. - Lots of it. I need lots of it.
我能用一下你的包嗎
Sh-should I use your bag?
拿去
Take it.
我現在要把它還給你  可以嗎
I'm going to pass this back to you now. Is that okay?
有個家伙站在那邊打電話把我嚇壞了
There was some bloke standing there on his phone freaking me out.
-你拿到了嗎  -是的
- Did you get it? - Yeah.
開快點
Go faster.
限速40  你想被抓超速嗎
Speed limit's 40. Wanna get stopped for speeding now?
-糟了  -操
- Oh, shit. - Fuck!
紅燈亮時  在此等待
有警笛聲
That's a siren.
別說話
Shush.
紅燈亮時  在此等待
-我們走吧  -閉嘴
- Let's go! - Shut up.
等等
Wait, wait.
快
Come on.
好的
Okay.
我們沒事了
We're okay.
我們應該給他們發短信
We should text them, no?
告訴他們我們拿到錢了
Tell them we got the money.
-他們說我們得把錢送到一個地方  -什么地方
- They say we got to take it somewhere. - Where?
就是這里
This is it.
是的
Yeah.
來了
Here we go.
"最終指示"
"Final instruction."
"把車開走并毀掉"
"Take car away and destroy."
把車毀掉
Destroy the car.
"你自己來"
"Just you alone."
為什么要你自己
Why just you?
一條新信息  來自未知號碼
把錢送到那個點
兩條新信息  來自未知號碼
自己來
我得把錢送到那邊
I got to take the money somewhere over there.
為什么  為什么要我去
Why? Why have I got to do it?
誰他媽知道
Fuck knows.
三條新信息  來自未知號碼
現在
那么...
So...
你最好去  對吧
You better go, yeah?
你都到這一步了  不是嗎
Hey, you got this far, haven't you?
把它放在那里  就完了
Just drop it off. That's it.
你不會有事的
You'll be all right.
聽我說  肯尼
Hey, listen, Kenny.
剛才的事...我很抱歉
Look. I'm sorry about-- just back there.
對你吼  還對你說臟話
Shouting at you. Calling you stuff.
我其實不是什么壞人  我發誓  只要...
I'm an all right bloke really. I swear I am, when it's--
一切正常
When stuff's normal.
你保重  好嗎
You take care, yeah?
等等  等一下
Yeah, yeah. Hang on, hang on.
他們跟我說我得先把它放飛
They told me I had to set this thing off first.
好了
Okay.
你拿來獎金了嗎
You got the prize money?
-什么獎金  -就是  給決斗準備的
- Prize money? - You know, for the... fight?
決什么斗
How is there a fight?
-他們沒跟你說嗎  -沒有
- They didn't tell you?  - No.
我們必須要決斗
We've got to fight...
不然他們就會把掌握的材料都公布出去
...or else they post everything they've got on us.
勝者獲得獎金
Winner takes the money.
我們必須得這么干
We've got to do it.
我是說
I mean...
他們看著呢
They're watching.
哪種決斗啊  我們怎么知道什么時候結束
What sort of fight? How do we know when it's over?
怎么算是贏啊
How... how do we know who's won?
你什么情況我不知道
I don't know about you, but
我的要是泄露了就完了
my life's over if this gets out.
我就他媽完了
Fucking over.
他們抓住你什么把柄了
What they get you for?
我就看了幾張照片
I just looked at some photos.
沒別的了  我就是看了一兩張照片
That's all. I just looked at one or two photos.
是啊
Yeah.
嗯  我也是就看了幾張照片
Yeah, yeah, I just looked at pictures too.
照片里的人有多大
How young were they? In the pictures?
多大
How young?
沒錯
Yeah.
我也是
Well, me too.
開打吧
打死為止
聽著  哥們  別這樣  求你
Look, mate. Don't. Please.
求你了
Please.
明迪
Mindy?
執行總裁身陷種族歧視郵件門
你就成這種人了嗎
Is that what you've become?
-一個骯臟猥瑣惡心的變態  -放松
- A dirty, sick, disgusting pervert?  - Hey, relax!
看著我  你就是這種人嗎
Look at me! Is that what you are?
媽媽來電
你干了什么肯尼  他們說那上面是小孩
What did you do, Kenny? They're saying it's kids!
你看的都是小孩
That you've been looking at kids!
琳賽也看到了  有一個你的視頻
And Lindsey saw it. There's a video of you.
你干的好事  她所有的朋友也都收到了
You're doing like... All of her friends have got it!
小孩啊  肯尼  告訴我這不是真的
Kids, Kenny! Tell me that's not true!
一條新消息  來自未知號碼